<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Running IT</title>
    <link>https://runningit.se/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Running IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://runningit.se/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure As Code Blog part 1 Godaddy with Terraform</title>
      <link>https://runningit.se/blog/iac_blog_part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://runningit.se/blog/iac_blog_part1/</guid>
      <description>Background As you know if you have read my last blog entry  I use GitHub to host my static page and Azure Pipeline for CI/CD. I have chosen Godaddy to be my DNS provider, the biggest reason behind this is that Azure and Godaddy have a partnership and I want to keep things simple. Godaddy is also big enough for other people to develop nice Terraform plugins, something that is missing in the Swedish DNS providers i have looked in to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo github CI using azure devops</title>
      <link>https://runningit.se/blog/azure_hugo_ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://runningit.se/blog/azure_hugo_ci/</guid>
      <description>Basic requirements  Trigger CI system at PR (pull request) Give feedback to the user that the PR have passed When I merge the pull, automatically publish my updated blog.  The last one is already solved thanks to that i use GitHub static page to share my homepage.
Tools My plan is to use the following tools:
 Azure Pipelines GitHub hub Hugo Yaspeller (to help me with my crappy spelling)  The reason why I chose Hugo as a static page generator is that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to use Jekyll (don&amp;rsquo;t like ruby) and it feels like a much more modern any way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>https://runningit.se/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://runningit.se/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>Hello Internet So It&amp;rsquo;s time for me to get a blog.
Heads up, I like to explain how I think when I write, so some parts might be a bit drawn out. But hopefully this place might be useful for you as well.
I will mostly use this blog to write about IT but it&amp;rsquo;s possible I will mention something about running or any of my other interests.
I think all of us have tested some tool that seemed cool and then didn&amp;rsquo;t start to use it day to day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>